Guide to the Department of Zoology records, 1873-1965.
Department of Zoology records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Department of Zoology records, 1873-1965.
14-26-966
Cornell University. Department of Zoology.
13 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, printed material, publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes personnel files, records, photographs, inventories and other departmental records.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes personnel files and records of applicants for positions, including correspondence of Howard D. Adelmann and letters and grade transcripts of applicants; information concerning fellowships, scholarships, and assistantships; examinations; student grade cards; reports; memoranda; news releases; inventory book of equipment; slides, photographs, and demonstration materials in the Zoology Department, and formulas and instructions for use in a zoological laboratory; seminar, conference, and committee records; report on room estimates for a new building, entitled "Space Requirements in Proposed New Animal Biology Building"; photographs of lampreys, eels, and toads; letters from Professor Edward Bradford Titchener to Professor Simon Henry Gage; a one volume record of zoological specimens, including a partial list of the brain collection of Burt Green Wilder; and other records of the Cornell Zoology Department. Also includes material pertaining to buildings and grounds, the University Policy Committee, the National Science Foundation, and other topics.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Adelmann, Howard B. (Howard Bernhardt), 1898-; Gage, Simon Henry, 1851-1944.; Titchener, Edward Bradford, 1867-1927.; Wilder, Burt Green, 1841-1925.; Cornell University -- Buildings.; Cornell University -- Examinations -- Zoology.; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University. Dept. of Zoology -- Admission.; Cornell University. Dept. of Zoology -- Funds and scholarships.; Cornell University. Dept. of Zoology -- Graduate students.; Cornell University. Summer Session.; Cornell University. Policy Committee.; Cornell University. Wilder Brain Collection.; National Science Foundation (U.S.)
Subjects:
Eels.; Lampreys.; Toads.; Zoology.; Zoology -- Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Slides (photographs).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also the Burt Green Wilder papers, #14-26-95, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA00095
See also the Albert Hazen Wright papers, #14-26-1382, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA01382
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence and Paper Review, 1893-1903 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Notes on Lampreys and Amphibians, 1875-1897 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Analytic Key and Systematic List of the Species of Fishes, Including Lampreys, of the Cayuga Lake Basin, N. Y. by H. A. Surface, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Leaflet on toads and Article on animals, including toads, 1895-1898 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  "Mother Nature's Children. III. Setting the Table. Part II.--Monkeys to Spiders." Nature Studies. Volume I, No. 10. Western Unitarian Sunday School Society: Chicago. Nov. 17, 1895.
- Newspaper clippings on animals and zoological techniques, 1873-1916 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Includes a handwritten poem addressed to the faculty of Cornell
- Newspaper clippings on animals and zoological techniques, 1873-1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series I. Histology Department Accounting
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1909-1911 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1911-1914 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1914-1916 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1922-1928 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Histology Department Accounting, 1928-1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1944-1945
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Academic Advising, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Agriculture, Communications re., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Agriculture, Extension Inquiries, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Agriculture, College of, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Applications: Library, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Assistantships, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Biology building, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Dissecting Kits, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Eadie, W. Robert, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Faculty of Agriculture - List of Standing Committees, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Fee Lists, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Fellowships, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - G, correspondents by last name Includes a copy of the article "A Hormone-Produced Taxonomic Character in Platypoecilus maculatus Diagnostic of Wild P. Xiphidium" from the American Naturalist, Vol. LXXVII. pages 569-572, November-December, 1943, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Gage, Simon Henry Includes obituary, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Gibson, A. W., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Graduate School Includes a copy of the Preliminary Draft of a Report from the Committee on Graduate Work, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Guterman, C. E. F., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - General - correspondence concerning the retirement of Mary Mekeel and Amy W. Mekeel, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - J, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Murdock, Carleton C., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Navy, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Ogden, R. M., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Peterson, Arthur H., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Projects - Cornell University Agricultural Experimentation Station, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Purchasing Department, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Resignation Forms, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Retirement Plan for Non-Academic Employees, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Sabine, George H., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Sibley, R. P., 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Staff Communications, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Technician position, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - U, correspondents by last name, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Vocation Applicants, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Wheeler, R. H., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Y, correspondents by last name, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1945-1946
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Admissions, Office of, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Agriculture, Faculty of, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Applicants for Biological Illustrator Position, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Assistantships, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Assistantships continued Includes "The Effect of Thyroxin Injections on the Thyrotrophin Content of the Anterior Pituitary of the Male Albino Mouse", Adams, Elizabeth A and Dorothy Jensen. Endocrinology, Vol. 35, No. 5, November 1944, 296-308., 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Assistantships continued, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Applications: Staff, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Conference for Discussion of Curriculum on Wildlife Conservation, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Committee, University Music, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Conservation, School of, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Dean, Office of, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Department of Zoology, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1946-1946 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Extension Work in Zoology, Program of, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Federal Aid, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Fees, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Furniture, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Gibson, A. W., 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Graduate Program, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Graduate Student Applications, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Gilbert, Perry W., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Graf-Apsco Co., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Graham, Edward K., 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Graduate School, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Graduate School Faculty, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Graduate School, General Committee of, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School Records, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Guterman, C. E. F., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Hertel, J. P., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Histology Courses, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - I, correspondents by last name, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Inventory, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - J, correspondents by last name, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ornithology Laboratory, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Payroll, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Photographic Science Service, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Physiology Laboratory Includes architectural drawings of Stimson Hall, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Purchasing Department, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Research Projects, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Robinson, M. E., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Sabine, George H., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Salary Payment, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Sibley, R. P., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Science Service, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Staff Communications, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Selective Service, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Summer Term, 1943-1946 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Thomas, Arthur H. Company, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Trimester System, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - U, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - University Employment Office, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Vocation Applicants, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Vertebrate Zoology, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Vertebrate Zoology Curator, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Victory Tax, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Wheeler, R. H., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Wildlife Control, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Y, correspondents by last name, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1946-1947
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Applications, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Assistantships, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Employment Services, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Enrollment Estimates, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Equipment, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Faculty, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Gibson, A. W., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Graduate School, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Graduate School Applicants, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Guterman, C. E. F., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Hertel, J. P., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Housing for Faculty, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - I, correspondents by last name, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Illustrator, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - J, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Library, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Microscopes, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Music Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Peterson, Arthur H., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Project Statements, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Provost, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Robinson, M. E., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Stumpf, John, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Societies: Phi Beta Kappa, Phi Kappa Phi, Research Club, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Summer Session, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Survey of Introductory Zoology, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Tuition, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - U, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - University Policy, Committee on, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Vocation Applicants, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Veterans Education, Office of, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Wheeler, R. H., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Wildlife Control, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Z, correspondents by last name, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Zoology Department, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1947-1948
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Experimentation Station, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture Department, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, College of Includes Course list for the Zoology Department, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Assistantships, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Assistantships continued, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Cole, LaMont C., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Committees and Conferences Includes "Science in General Education at the College Level," Taylor, Lloyd W. Science, June 14, 1940, Vol. 91, No. 2372, apges 560-565., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Department of Zoology, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Department General Order, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Department Annual Inventory, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Department - Van Cleef Memorial Library Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Department Development Period, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Department Letters of Recommendation, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Department of Zoology Seminar, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Gibson, A. W., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Graduate School, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Graduate School Records, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - I, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Machine Shop Memorandum, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Michigan, University of, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Music Committee, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - N, O, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Peterson, Arthur H., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - President Edmund E. Day, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Provost, Office of the, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Report on Fall 1947 Admissions, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Science in General Education, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Summer Session, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Student Technician, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Trustees, Board of, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - University Library Board, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - University Policy Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - University Positions, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Veterans Education Office, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Wheeler, R. H., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Will Corporation, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Wright Book Fund, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1948-1949
    - A, correspondence by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Abbott, Frank C., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Agassiz and Cornell, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Administrative Officers, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Agricultural Experimentation Station, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - American Optical Company, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Applications, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Assistantships, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Arts and Sciences Questionnaire, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Arantius, Iulius Caesar, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Business, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Cole, LaMont C., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Committee on Educational Policy, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Committee on University Policy, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Department of Zoology, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Department General Order, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Department Annual Inventory, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Division of Cancer Research, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Department Graduate Program, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Department Graduate Students, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Exhibits for Cornell's Eightieth Anniversary, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Graduate School, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Graduate School Records, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Greater Cornell Fund Includes Cornell Booklet "Names That Endure", 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Hamilton, W. J., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - I, J, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Laughlin, William S., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Leonard, Dr., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Loan, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Myers, W. I., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - N, O, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Peterson, Arthur H., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Position, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - P. A. S. Project, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Purchasing Department, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Q, R, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Reichmann, Felix, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Stimson Hall Basement Alterations, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Stimson Hall Third Floor Alterations, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Sigma Xi, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Arthur L., 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - State of New York Report, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Summer Session, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Terwillegar, R. E., 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Numbers, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - University Faculty, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)